Hey! Raimon!
What's with the bike?!
You can't just ride a motorcycle
to school without permission!
Aight.
What are you, a hooligan?!
Takaragi, you should have stopped her, too!
Well...
She's the one who told me not to be late.
And I live real far from school,
so it's a royal pain in the ass.
That's hooligan talk!
Knock it off!
But I'm glad... you came to school...
Stardust Telepath
Episode 5
Endless Dreamer
Raimon-san.
Ever since middle school,
I've always admired her confidence.
We challenged her to a bottle rocket contest.
I may have lost that match, but I finally
told her what was on my mind.
I'm glad to see Raimon-san
back at school again!
Konohoshi-san, bona-morning!
G-Good... mati...
Yu, bona-morning!
Mativuu, Nasshi!
She has been learning the violin
since she was five years old,
and she is aiming for music
college in the future!
Good!
Next, roster number fourteen.
Number fourteen?
Y-Yes!
Yes!
It's x squared!
This is English class!
Huh?
Don't doze off in class!
Sure!
Hey, hey!
Matataki, come eat lunch with us!
Leave me alone, bun-haired nutjob.
Let's try asking her again tomorrow.
Sure!
You don't have to rush your meal.
Cream of Potato
Nice and Hot
I survived another whole day of school!
Nothing beats some creamy potato soup
for wrapping up the day!
Good job, Matataki!
Here! Let's share a can!
You don't ever dial it down, do you?
Feel free to take a nice, big gulp!
I don't want your leftovers.
Yu seems happier than usual today!
I bet it's because you're here,
Matataki-chan.
I shouldn't have come to school.
I can't stand all this yapping.
Oh? Is someone embarrassed?
Like hell I am!
That stubborn attitude is just
hiding your embarrassment!
Shut up! I'll tear off those buns of yours!
Matataki-chan looks like
she's having fun, too.
R-Raimon-san.
Was there anything today
th-that gave you trouble?
I-If there's anything you need,
just let me know.
I-I'll do what I-I can to help!
Oh, well, not really.
You should worry about yourself first.
Huh? B-But...
I'll be fine.
This girl...
When she was launching rockets with
Haruno and the bun-haired nutjob,
I thought she showed some guts...
But the moment she's thrown into
a school setting, she turns into this.
Well, guess I'm not one to talk,
considering I wasn't attending at all.
Hey, Matataki!
I wanna try launching a cool
rocket like the one back then!
And you're the same wherever you go.
I wish you could lend her
some of that backbone.
Well, it's not a bad idea.
It can serve as your next step up.
I-I'd love to make one!
I'm all for it!
The parts don't come cheap, though,
so the one problem is the money.
How much can you spare in club funds?
W-We're not, um, in a club or anything...
It's all out-of-pocket!
Just call us free dreamers!
What?!
Without any means of funding, you won't
even be able to make rockets for fun!
Here, look!
Itemized expenses necessary
for a bona-fide rocket launch!
I summed it all up, so read it over!
Bil         Bil
10 billion yen
She took the time to look it up...
This is when you need to bleed 'em dry
for everything they've got!
Teachers' Office
Everyone knows that!
Sensei, club!
Who're you calling a club?! Knock it off!
Oh, it's you girls.
What's up?
We're very sorry to interrupt you.
We were hoping to start up a new club,
so could we please have an application form?
Oh, an application form?
There ya go.
Thank you very much.
You could learn something from Haruno.
You're the last one I want to hear that from!
Summary of club activities.
"Rocket assembly" should do.
What should we name the club?
Yes, yes!
A flash of inspiration!
Club Name
Dream*Rocket Club
New Club Application Form
Registration date: 5/22
1. Club name
Dream*Rocket Club
2. Summary of club activities
Rocket assembly, demonstrations, research
3. Club accomplishments (optional)
Launched bottle rockets and
measured their flight distances.
The Dream*Rocket Club!
Huh? Lame!
It's a one-of-a-kind name.
You wrote this in pen?
Now I can't erase it!
Well, whatever.
Anything else missing?
Okay, that should do it!
Let's go!
Teachers' Office
Wait, am I thinking of the right rockets?
The kind that fly?
The kind that fly into outer space!
O-Outer space?!
Our school is pretty lenient when it comes
to extracurricular activities, but...
Can you give me an idea with a
better chance of getting accepted?
You can just say it's a volunteer club, then.
Whatever works.
Be a little pickier than that! Pickier!
Well, which is it?!
Um...
W-We're... s-serious about this...
Blah           blah
yadda           yadda
Umika and I are trying
to go out into space!
Now, the school already
has an astronomy club,
Assembling models
of solid-propellant rockets
I've a-always been interested
in rockets and outer space...
You need a rocket
for that, right?!
will be the key focus of our
activities for the time being.
but their primary goal
is to observe the stars.
A-And we all tried
making bottle rockets...
While they may be replicas,
we are building real rockets,
So we need to make one,
and Matataki said...
In contrast, our goal is
to research and develop
so parts like the frame and
engine cost a significant amount.
N-Now, we want to make
something more advanced...
methods for going
to outer space!
Huh...
So that's what you've been up to.
I had no idea!
That's because we were working in secret!
Are you okay with this?
The secret's out of the bag.
We'll make an exception
for you, Emihara-sensei.
I see, I see.
Okay! Got it.
I'll see what I can do to get it greenlit!
Really?!
You betcha!
So come up with a more
concrete idea by next week!
O-Okay!
Also!
New Club Application Form
Registration date: 5/22
1. Club name
Dream*Rocket Club
2. Summary of club activities
Rocket assembly, demonstrations, research
3. Club accomplishments (optional)
Launched bottle rockets and
measured their flight distances.
Think of a snazzier name for the club, too!
What?!
I was so proud of that name!
No surprise there.
Thank you very much!
Th-Thank you... very much...
I hope we can secure some club funds.
Then we can make a big ol' rocket!
That sounds lovely!
How large should it be?
It's because I want to find
a place where I belong.
Good for you.
Weren't you looking for a place to belong?
Now you have one, so good for you.
I-I mean...
N-Never mind.
O-Oh, yeah!
That club form just now!
I took the liberty of filling out
who'd be in charge, too.
So good luck with your new position, prez.
What's going on?
What are you talking about?
She's going to be our club president.
That sounds great!
Oh! I wanna be vice president!
Overruled.
Haruno, you do it.
What? Me?!
Why her?!
Boy, what a surprise, though.
4. Activity schedule
Weekdays until ~5:30 PM every week
5. List of club members
Class 1-A #3:
Yu Akeuchi
Class 1-A #19: Haruno Takaragi
Class 1-A #14: Umika Konohoshi
(president)
Class 1-A #29: Matataki Raimon
6. Remarks
None in particular
I took her to be one of
my more reserved students,
but Konohoshi as president?
And Raimon's in the club, at that!
Maybe this form is proof that a
tiny spark can set off big changes.
I need to make sure this goes through,
no matter what!
W-Well, l-looks like it'll be a little
longer before we can begin our club.
Yes.
We'll need to first discuss
what our club will do.
Just come up with something
that sounds good during class.
During class...
I saw you working on something else.
I bet I didn't miss anything interesting.
Ah!
Matataki's a hooligan!
Cram it!
I saw you sleeping the whole time!
Well, tomorrow's another day of
showing up to school whenever,
and doing whatever I like at my desk, right?
Maybe school's easier than I thought.
Why are you giving me that look?
C'mon, now!
Don't tell me you forgot, Matataki!
A-About what?
I gave you the notice, didn't I?
A few weeks ago
Here's a handout from school.
It's very important,
so make sure you look it over.
I'll use it as scratch paper.
Tomorrow, the first-years are going
on a two-day study camp!
Yep!
What?
What?!
This is news to me!
Let's make it a trip to remember!
Stardust Telepath
Lately, it feels as though
I'm surrounded by sparkles.
Launching a bottle rocket
for the first time...
Going shopping with my friends...
Becoming friends with Raimon-san...
These sparkles...
What lies behind the sparkling...
No,
spinning?
Umika!
Umika-chan!
Sensei!
Umika-chan's feeling short of breath!
What?!
We're still at the base of the mountain!
Everyone! Good work making the climb!
Are you feeling better?
I know we just made it to the building,
Yeah.
but it's time for our workshop!
Okay!
I trust you've looked over the reading
materials I gave out in advance?
Get into your groups!
Not a lot of happy campers, huh?
Weary...
Choosing this high school was a mistake.
Okay, that's the most dramatic
reaction I've ever gotten.
Matataki-chan!
We're in the same group!
We'll see you two later!
Lemme go home.
Don't say that.
I think you'll enjoy some of the reading!
Yeah, right.
What do we need to do for this workshop?
W-Well...
Literature
Religion
History
Environmental conservation
Heritage site
Plant and animal life
Fine art
U-Using the given documents
and literary works
written about th-this mountain's
surrounding environment,
e-each group will d-decide on
a topic and create a report.
Docu...ments?
You did get them in advance, right?
Conference Room 1
All right, then!
Let's begin the workshop!
I'm Kagami, group leader and class president,
and I'll be in charge of the proceedings!
Let's all work hard together!
First, let's take turns and share the reading
that you thought was most interesting!
I thought... the essay on
page 21 was interesting...
Umika!
Because...
How do you read this kanji?
Do you think she'll be okay?
Doesn't look like it to me.
If only Takaragi-san and
Raimon-san were in our group.
Okay, next, can you tell us what
you thought, Konohoshi-san?
M-My mind's gone completely blank!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh...
I-I thought the essay on
page 21 was i-interesting.
Study Camp
Workshop Reading
Literature
B-Because...
th-this author's novels a-always
take place in w-winter,
b-but this essay alone uses
spring as its theme...
This is... sort of fun!
I always hated being in situations like this,
but not this time!
Everything's sparkling again.
It's all because I met Akeuchi-san.
Good for you.
If all goes well with the club,
I can do more for Akeuchi-san.
That reminds me, after that...
So good luck with your new position, prez.
Sh-She must have been kidding about that!
I-I-I can't be club president!
I can't help but worry just
as I'm about to go to sleep!
That reminds me, Akeuchi-san still
hasn't come back from the bathroom.
Wait!
Did she end up being abducted
by a fellow alien?!
Umika! Help me!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What do I do?!
She's nowhere to be found.
Where could she have gone?
Akeuchi-san!
What a relief!
Umika!
Why are you out here?
You'll catch a cold!
I-I was worried because
you didn't come back.
Sheesh!
You're such a worrywart, Umika!
Did you think I ended up being abducted?
Look at that, Umika!
The sky!
It's sparkling like crazy!
There's lots more stars than usual!
I found myself lost in thought out here,
wondering whether one of these
could be my home planet.
A-Akeuchi-san...
My bad!
Forget it, forget it!
Forget what I just said!
Um, well, it's not like
I feel lonely or anything!
You know that I love life here on Earth!
Besides...
W-We'll make it!
We'll make it into space! I swear it!
Akeuchi-san has always been there
to guide my dreams and my words.
Which is why it's my turn now!
Y-You know...
Back when we first met, I think...
my dream wasn't a very realistic one.
B-But that's not true anymore!
T-Takaragi-san and Raimon-san
are here to help us now!
A-And our new club, too.
So I promise I'll take you there!
I-I'll be the one to make
all your wishes come true!
Ah, um...
I-I can't put it into words very well.
But the truth is, I have lots more to...
I swear, Umika...
I want to hear your words.
All of them, to the very end.
Please tell me.
Ah, my bad.
Wait...
Wh-Why am I the one apologizing?!
What on earth are you two
It's foreheadpathy!
The hell is that?!
Wh-What are you two doing here?
Heads up!
Tyrant Soul
30 Shots
Firework Rocket
Coco Cola
Firework rockets.
You said you've never touched one, right?
We'll be fine, Onee-chan.
Let's give those rotten teachers
snoozing away a good scare!
A once-in-a-lifetime chance
to make priceless memories...
Yes, I'm sure even God will
turn a blind eye to this sin!
Multi-Shot Fireworks
Waterfall
Ascent
Coco Cola
Kirara
Fireworks
Lightning
Flash
Firework
Rocket
Let's set off the big rockets
at the same time.
Won't that be dangerous?
It'll be totally fine.
Shaking in your boots yet, prez?
No, I'm fine!
My tiny dream is moving forward,
little by little.
I know that this dream isn't
just a fairy tale now!
With everyone's help,
I'm going to make it a reality!
Multi-Shot Fireworks
Waterfall
Ascent
Danger!
Do not hold!
Kirara
Fireworks
Lightning
Flash
Firework
Rocket
I promise I'll get stronger
to make that happen!
Umika!
Thanks.
We'll go to space for sure!
Okay, next up...
There!
Haruno?!
Hey!
Matataki...
S-Stop it!
Let go... Hey!
But actually, it's Umika!
How come?!
Oh, my!
Episode 6
Salutatory Initiation
Salutatory Initiation!