Onee-chan's watching her speech again.
Hey. Hold on, Haruno.
Don't stop the video.
Our chairwoman can do it.
Keep recording until the end.
Raimon-san...
Stardust Telepath
Episode 11
Rematching Seaside
Umika!
Bonavuu!
Bona-morning!
I got here first today!
Sorry I'm late...
You're still here 30 minutes early.
Huh?
Takaragi-san, are those...
I swiped them from Matataki-chan!
Swiped?!
Hi-yah!
I-I see.
* Artist's impression
So you met Raimon-san yesterday.
I was all fired up from the power
that I got from you two.
But we ended up kind of fighting in the end.
There were a lot more things
I wanted to say...
It's not easy, huh?
Th-That's amazing, Takaragi-san!
Y-Y-You did great!
Umika-chan...
Aw, yeah!
Time to infuse Haruno with some more power
so she can get fired up again!
M-Me too!
I'm at max forehead power!
Now Umika-chan's secret plan
is sure to be a rousing success!
W-Well, l-last night...
Sorry for springing it on you all of a sudden.
Um...
It's fine.
I was sure that's what you would do, anyway.
So true!
Look!
I brought my rockets!
The one I made in club, and one
I made in secret as practice!
Me too!
Now we just need Kei to get here!
Model rocket spotted!
I lured her in!
Kei-san!
Sorry I'm late!
I went to the wrong place!
Thanks for messaging me last night.
Our club was meeting today anyway,
so it all worked out.
Um, well...
W-We want to get b-better at
making rockets all by ourselves!
Thank you for taking the time to teach us!
Mentee Aura!!
S-So dazzling!
An unfamiliar school.
So shiny!
Our club room's this way!
Hey! Neon-senpai!
We're having guests over,
so please clean this place up!
Space R&D Club
What?
Can't we just eat snacks together like this?
I'm going to tell Kei-senpai!
There you go tattling again!
Tattletales get a tickling!
We're outside.
We can hear everything.
Michiru Yugumo
I'll be looking forward to it.
Tickle, tickle!
Enter a message
I'll be looking forward to it.
We're outside.
We can hear everything.
Stop that!
Read
Space R&D Club
What?
Hey, there!
I'm Neon Teruya, a second-year!
W-Welcome.
I'm Michiru Yugumo, a first-year.
H-H-H-Hello, we're...
We know, we know.
No need to be so formal.
O-Okay.
Isn't it amazing?
Please don't brag about
Kei-senpai's collection.
Let's cut to the chase:
show us all of your rockets!
Y-Yes!
I-I'd love some advice.
I-I tried l-launching it m-myself,
b-but the trajectory and parachute
didn't go as p-planned.
The fin angles are off.
Isn't the connection too tight?
The center of gravity is a bit low.
You've got three fins, so they should
be attached 120 degrees apart.
Y-Yes.
I-I thought I was being
c-careful when I glued them.
It's not easy going off
just your hands and eyes.
For the gluing, you should
use a jig, like this.
I have a blueprint I made, so I'd
be happy to share it with you.
Check out Kei-chan,
playing up the mentor act!
A-Am not!
For the part where you insert the parachute,
let's loosen it by sanding
down the connecting piece!
Check the center of gravity
by hanging it from a string,
with the engine temporarily in place.
Let's make it a little heavier at the top.
These small changes should
have improved it quite a bit.
Whoa, that's amazing!
Raimon-san did all of the important
parts for us until now,
so I didn't know...
any of this...
No matter how confident you are
in the rocket you've built,
you won't know whether it'll work
until you actually launch it.
There are so many unknowns.
All of the adjustments I'm making...
They're all lessons I've learned
from my own failures.
If you don't know,
then you've just got to learn!
Keep on building rockets and launching them!
If you mess up, then fix it!
If there's something you don't know,
ask someone else!
And, little by little, you can end up
with something that's proven to work.
Oh, that's right.
How's Raimon-san doing?
Um...
Sh-She hasn't been coming to school.
Oh...
Then let's surprise Raimon-san
the next time you see her!
Show her just how much you've learned!
Right!
Okay, let's try launching it right now!
Right here!
Here?!
We have model rocket simulation
software installed.
In a virtual world, you can mess up
all you like without straining your wallet!
M-Makes sense.
I've been waiting for ten minutes!
It's my turn on the computer!
Nuh-uh.
I'm in the middle of something.
C'mon, no need to get so heated.
Let's all take turns!
I don't want to hear that from someone who
hogged the computer for six hours yesterday.
I want to watch aerial videos
with Takaragi-san!
Um, I don't mind waiting...
I brought my own laptop today,
so let's use this.
Mentor Act
A Engine
B Engine
1/2A Engine
Using the software, you can also easily
compare the estimated altitudes
for the same rocket launched
with different engines.
Let's try it out with engines that match
the dimensions of your rocket!
You get totally different altitudes
with an A and a B engine!
That's pure performance difference
between the two engines.
Let's see what it looks like
with wind added in!
Th-Thank you very much for today!
Same here!
It spurred me on as well.
Kei-chan tried so hard to
be a good mentor today,
but that's not what she's usually like.
That's right.
She'll forget to submit tournament
entries without batting an eye.
Hey!
She always forgets to insert
the wadding in the rocket.
She's always short on money, because she
uses all her part-time earnings on rockets.
Th-That's not even relevant here!
Seriously, if I wasn't there for her...
Feel free to visit again any time!
How was it?
It was interesting.
The shm... sh... sims, for example.
We got to learn a lot.
U-Until now, we were p-putting
a lot of burden on Raimon-san.
But...
I-If we practice, w-we can build
rockets that are just as good!
Now you just need to follow
that secret plan of yours!
You've gotta make the first move to win!
Seize the momentum!
Go on, Umika!
Let's show her our power!
Yeah!
Leave it to your chairwoman!
Letter
Don't you lose either.
R-Raimon-san!
It's Umika!
C-Come out!
Letter of Challenge
Co—
Ah, um...
L-Long time no see!
W-Well, l-l...
Let's have a rocket contest!
I-I-If you refuse, th-that means I w-win!
Okay.
We did promise to have another duel.
Let's do it.
I'm sure this will be the last time.
Stardust Telepath
The weather's great.
Perfect for launching rockets.
I'm all ready on my end.
Hurry up and get ready.
Let's finish this before
the wind changes direction.
R-Raimon-san, promise me.
I-If we win, you'll l-listen
to what we have to say.
That's all you ever say, huh?
Yeah, yeah. Sure thing.
But that's only if you win.
We'll win for sure.
Matataki, we're going by your rules, right?
Yeah, no changes from me.
We each launch a rocket with an A8-3 engine,
and whichever reaches
the higher altitude wins.
Nice and simple.
You get one shot only for the launch.
We'll use altimeters for our measurements,
and load one on board
each rocket as the payload.
Okay.
Beat me if you can.
The value on the altimeter...
I'll tell you what it was
when you get your results.
Now it's your turn.
Get a move on already.
Takaragi-san?
Oh, it's nothing.
We should make sure our rocket
doesn't get blown away by the wind.
It's been two weeks since we
promised to have this duel.
We've done the best we could, and we've
given it plenty of thought and practice.
To reduce the weight,
we got help from Akizuki-san in making our own body tube from scratch.
We've also performed real test launches
with the altimeter on board.
There have been days
with worse wind than this.
There were days when we failed,
but even those served to
help us make improvements.
So today...
Today's the one day...
where we need to win!
Our rocket reached 76 meters,
and Matataki's was 31 meters.
We beat her.
So I lost, huh?
I didn't think I'd lose so badly.
Guess I was a bit sloppy
with my build quality.
Well, what's done is done.
Now you understand.
You don't need me.
The results just now proved that.
You'll be plenty fine on your own without me.
So you can save your little
speech or whatever.
Why...
Huh?
Hey!
1/2A... I knew it.
Why did you use a less powerful engine?
I figured that was enough
to beat the likes of you.
That's a lie!
Didn't I tell you not to lose?
I'd meant it as a handicap,
but you handily trounced me.
Just means I was that much of an idiot.
The results are what they are.
Why won't you see the light already?
There's no point in sticking around
someone as pathetic as me.
I suggest you look for a
better engineer next time.
I mean, you're trying to get
to outer space, aren't you?
So you should just cut ties with me...
for... good...
What?
What are you crying for?
I didn't say anything to make you cry.
Get off—
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't understand what
you were going through.
I'm sorry.
I'm... I'm weak,
so I thought this whole time
that I didn't belong here.
That I w-was the only one who felt
weak, miserable, and in pain.
Which is why I always wanted to be like you
a-and be strong enough to brush off
all of those worries.
But I was wrong!
That wasn't true at all!
You, and everyone else...
were all the same.
A reason to be here...
A reason to stay here...
A place where you belong...
This whole time...
This whole time, that's what
you were looking for.
And I couldn't even realize that!
Shut up!
Don't act like you know how I feel!
Is that the winner's high-and-mighty wisdom?!
Are you happy taking pity on the loser?!
To hell with that!
That's not what I'm looking for!
Don't you... any of you...
dare to act like we're the same!
I've had enough of your empty words!
I'm not... I'm not...
Liar.
Those are all lies.
Matataki, your heart is an open book.
Y-You know, Raimon-san.
Everyone, including you,
gave me a reason to be here.
Because you y-yelled at me
for being useless back then,
I was able to gather up the
courage to tell you my dream.
B-Because you gave me the push
I needed to start a club,
I found a new place where
I belonged at school.
Even though I was c-convinced that
I didn't belong anywhere,
being with you, and everyone else,
gave me a place to belong.
That's why...
This time, I want to become
a place for you to belong!
One where you feel like you can stay.
I want to become that t-tiny reason for you!
L-Last time we faced off,
I was only able to talk about your goggles.
This time, I'll say it
for real, as your friend.
So listen.
Let's aim for the skies
together again, Raimon-san.
It was always the same.
I would selfishly lash out with harsh
words over the smallest matters,
and put an end to all of my relationships.
No one would give me the
convenience of another chance.
So there was no point putting hope in
relationships that only existed to be cut off.
Don't care. Don't care.
Don't care.
And yet...
Why?
Again and again...
Why?!
Didn't I say all those awful things to you?
I was hurtful in my actions,
time and time again.
When you say those things,
you're the one who's hurt the most.
I could tell all along.
I know you also stood the firmest out of all
of us, so that our group could move forward.
No!
That's not it.
I just wanted to win the match,
so I ignored all of you.
Always thinking about nothing but myself,
only to then lose horribly...
I really have nothing to show for it.
Nothing at all.
If it's all just going to disappear anyway,
I don't want any of it to begin with!
Your words, your pity, none of it!
They won't disappear.
My words, my feelings...
I'll keep trying as long as it takes.
I'll make sure they reach you.
So they're not going to disappear.
Other people's words are always
so vapid, worthless, empty.
Galactic Roar
Gunvalion
the Movie
To the Ends of Space
Lepdios
Taking them seriously
was just a waste of time.
Now we can all build model rockets together!
Thank you for today, Raimon-san!
I know that, so why,
instead of ignoring her words,
am I answering back with my own?
That's...
That's how I feel, too.
I was happy,
making rockets with all of you.
That's why I didn't want to lose it.
I really, really
didn't want to lose it.
Even now, the truth is...
I want to make rockets with you again.
Ah, damn it.
Why am I saying this?
Don't listen to my pathetic whining.
Sorry.
I know it's too late to apologize.
N-No...
I'm sorry.
Matataki!
I'm... I'm sorry too!
Me too.
I'm sorry!
You didn't do anything.
Umika. Yu. Haruno.
Sorry.
Thank you.
Wha—?!
You can't be the cool
Matataki-chan without these!
You moron.
There's nothing cool about me!
I lost to you!
Nope.
You haven't lost.
You haven't lost at all, Matataki-chan.
Not at all!
You're wide open!
It's all over once you've exposed
your forehead to an alien!
Umi-chairwoman, get 'er good!
Ah, um, okay!
R-Rub...
Rub, rub!
Hi-yah!
You'll pay for this.
I feel a lot better after crying!
Matataki, how about you?
I-I wasn't crying!
I know!
Let's go grab dinner on our way back!
Matataki's treat!
I'm not treating anyone.
Cheapskate!
Or, well...
If that's what you want,
I don't mind treating you.
Maruobeev tereev.
Huh? Say what?
"Tsundere alien."
Bun nut!
Stop right there!
Sounds like we're all going to go eat.
You called me by my name earlier!
Is that okay with you, Umika-chan?
Did not!
Matataki, you're such a maruobeev!
I-I'm...
Shut up, bun nut!
Umika!
The sudden wave of relief just took
all the strength out of my body.
Ah! She's burning up!
I-I'll call an ambulance!
I'm scared of ambulances.
Umika!
Stay with us!
Episode 12
Stardust Telepath
Stardust Telepath.
When Launching Model Rockets:
Make sure you have proper educator supervision.
Obtain all permission needed before launching rockets
or purchasing rocket parts like black powder or engines.
Always follow rules and regulations, and put safety first!